Welcome to the Cisco IT/OT Convergence course.
This is an interactive,
self-paced learning experience.
The course begins with a landing page where you can
scroll to read a course description and view the outline.
Your progress is automatically saved,
so you can pick up where you left off at any time.
As you move through the lessons,
each page will load dynamically as you scroll.
As you complete a page or section,
you will encounter a continue button that guides you forward.
On the left side of the screen,
you'll see a navigation menu showing the full course structure.
As you complete each page,
it will be marked as complete.
Each block of text is accompanied by an audio guide.
You can choose to read or listen.
The audio button in the bottom right opens a menu where you
can toggle the autoplay function on or off and adjust the volume.
Throughout the course,
you'll encounter many interactive activities.
Be sure to select each part of the interaction to view all the information.
You'll also encounter short knowledge checks along the way.
These are designed to help reinforce your understanding and review key points.
You must successfully complete each question to move on.
If you answer incorrectly,
you will receive corrective feedback and can try again.
This course will help you build
foundational knowledge of IT/OT converged environments,
while gaining hands-on experience with Cisco Cyber Vision.
When you're ready,
let's get started.